First Casualty Press Records
© 2002 University of Connecticut
- Series II: Writings, 1960-1978
  - Post Mortem, edited by Basil T. Paquet and Wayne Karlin (unpublished).
    - Submitted works by author
      - Atkin, Carol, undated (Box 15:322)
      - Boggis, Jay, undated, 1970, 1972 (Box 15:323)
      - Boyer, Dennis, undated (Box 15:324)
      - Childs, Geoffrey, undated (Box 15:325)
      - DiZazzo, Raymond, undated (Box 15:326)
      - Driscoll, Gregory, undated (Box 15:327)
      - Ellis, R. Joseph, undated (Box 15:328)
      - Fritzinger, Dennis, undated (Box 15:329)
      - Griffin, Tom, undated (Box 15:330)
      - Hassett, Steve, undated, 1971-1972 (Box 15:331)
      - Hathaway, W. Stephen, undated (Box 15:332)
      - Hounshell, William, undated, 1972-1973 (Box 15:333)
      - Hudak, E. J., undated (Box 15:334)
      - Johnson, Michael H., 1973 (Box 15:335)
      - Kemp, Don, undated (Box 15:336)
      - Kramer, Larry, 1973 Jul 18 (Box 15:337)
      - Levy, Marc, 1970-1972 (Box 15:338)
      - Mitchell, John, Jr., undated (Box 15:339)
      - Overholser, Stephen, undated (Box 15:340-342)
      - Porsche, Don, undated (Box 15:343)
      - Poulter, S.L., undated (Box 15:344)
      - Saner, Reginald A., undated (Box 15:345)
    - Publication History
      - Original TM, undated (Box 15:346)
      - Illustrative Materials, undated (Box 15:347)
      - Final Bound Draft, undated (Box 16)
  - General
    - Submitted works by unpublished author
      - Abbott, Gregory, undated (Box 17:348-351)
      - Adams, Bill, undated, 1968 (Box 17:352)
      - Anderson, R. A., undated (Box 17:353-354)
      - Anderson, Robert L., undated (Box 17:355)
      - Apple, Lynn N., undated (Box 17-18:356-358)
      - Baber, Asa, undated (Box 18:359)
      - Bartling, Peter B., undated, 1967 Mar 27 (Box 18:360)
      - Bayless, David, undated (Box 18:361)
      - Beattie, Paul, undated (Box 18:362)
      - Berenbak, Peter, undated (Box 18:363)
      - Berry, D.C., undated (Box 18:364)
      - Bittle, Camilla, undated (Box 18:365)
      - Blanco, Nathan, undated (Box 18:366)
      - Borden, Robert H., 1972 Mar 29 (Box 18:367)
      - Bravar, Stephen, undated (Box 18:368)
      - Bronder, Howard, 1973 Jan (Box 18:369)
      - Brown, Steven, undated (Box 18:370)
      - Chambers, Robert (Bob), undated (Box 18:371)
      - Chianelli, John P., undated (Box 18:372)
      - Clodfelter, Mike, undated (Box 18:373)
      - Cole, Lawrence, undated (Box 18:374)
      - Coleman, Horace, undated (Box 18:375)
      - Cote, Raymond W., undated (Box 18:376)
      - Deskin, Skip, undated (Box 18:377)
      - Dewey, Al A., undated (Box 18:378)
      - Dietz, Frederick W., Jr., undated (Box 18:379)
      - Duncan, Angus, undated (Box 18:380)
      - Earl-Clark, David, undated (Box 19:381)
      - Egendorf, Arthur, Jr., undated, 1968 May (Box 19:382)
      - Ettenson, Paul, 1968 Oct 29 (Box 19:383)
      - Feghorn, John, undated (Box 19:384)
      - Flanagan, Jim, undated (Box 19:385)
      - Forman, William H., Jr., undated (Box 19:386)
      - Flynn, Daniel, undated (Box 19:387)
      - Goldhammer, Art, undated (Box 19:388)
      - Goldstein, Harvey, undated (Box 19:389)
      - Gott, George, undated (Box 19:390)
      - Gottlieb, Ed, undated, 1960, 1972 (Box 19:391)
      - Gray, Amlin, undated (Box 19:392)
      - Greenwood, Bruce, 1972-1973 (Box 19:393)
      - Grothus, Edward, 1972 Nov 21 (Box 19:394)
      - Hall, Ralph, undated (Box 19:395)
      - Halvorsen, S., 1969-1973 (Box 19:396)
      - Hardin, E.R., undated (Box 19:397)
      - Harris, James Frances, 1970 (Box 19:398)
      - Hawley, Carroll, 1972 Oct 4 (Box 19:399)
      - Heinrichs, Ken, undated (Box 19:400)
      - Helman, B.F., undated (Box 19:401)
      - Holloway, Fred L., undated (Box 19:402)
      - Hulley, James J., undated (Box 19:403)
      - Hunt, Robert M., undated (Box 19:404)
      - Jackson, Daniel B., undated (Box 20:405)
      - Jacobson, Jake, undated (Box 20:406)
      - Jacobson, Philip, undated (Box 20:407)
      - Johnson, Michael, undated (Box 20:408)
      - Kingry, Phillip, 1971 Mar 3 (Box 20:409)
      - Lanzek, James, undated (Box 20:410)
      - Lawless, Gary, undated (Box 20:411)
      - Leinsdorf, Joshua, undated (Box 20:412)
      - Lerner, Charles, undated (Box 20:413)
      - Lewallen, John, undated (Box 20:414-415)
      - Livingston, Gordon S., undated (Box 20:416)
      - Lucas, Peter, undated (Box 20:417)
      - Lupo, Robert (Bob), undated (Box 20:418)
      - Madden, William, undated (Box 20:419)
      - Mahoney, Peter P., undated (Box 20:420)
      - Mann, Polly, undated, 1971 (Box 20:421)
      - Martin, Earl E., undated, 1968 (Box 20:422)
      - Martin-Trigona, Anthony R., undated (Box 21)
      - Maxham, Jerry, undated (Box 20:423)
      - McClelland, Barry R., undated (Box 20:424)
      - McCormack, Allen E., undated (Box 20:425)
      - McCurdy, Robert J., 1972 Sep 18 (Box 20:426)
      - McGarry, Thomas, undated (Box 20:427)
      - McLaughlin, Robert, undated (Box 22:428)
      - Merlati, Sam, undated (Box 22:429)
      - Meyerowitz, Lee, undated (Box 22:430)
      - Miller, Robert, 1968 Dec (Box 22:431)
      - Moore, Scott, undated, 1972 Jan (Box 22:432)
      - Munzell, Michael, undated (Box 22:433)
      - Needle, Jeff, undated, 1970 (Box 22:434)
      - Novak, David W, undated (Box 22:435)
      - Noyola, Robert, 1970-1971 (Box 22:436)
      - Olmstead, Charles W., 1967 (Box 22:437)
      - O'Meara, Rick, undated (Box 22:438)
      - O'Neill, John, undated, 1972 (Box 22:439)
      - Peterson, James M., undated (Box 22:440)
      - Peterson, Vernon, undated (Box 22:441)
      - Pierce, Brad, 1972 (Box 22:442)
      - Povey, George, undated (Box 22:443)
      - Preston, Charles S., 1972 (Box 22:444)
      - Primm, Alex, undated (Box 22:445-446)
      - Rendleman, Danny L., undated (Box 23:447)
      - Reser, Phil, undated (Box 23:448)
      - Richman, Elliot, undated (Box 23:449)
      - Riesenmy, Robert P., undated (Box 23:450)
      - Rogers, David, undated (Box 23:451)
      - Rotman, Richard E., 1973 (Box 23:452)
      - Rudoi, W.H., undated (Box 23:453)
      - Ruhl, Kipper, undated (Box 23:454)
      - Scahill, James Vincent, undated (Box 23:455)
      - Schlosser, Robert L., undated, 1969-1970 (Box 23:456)
      - Schuster, William, undated (Box 23:457)
      - Sessions, David, undated (Box 23:458)
      - Setian, Ralph, 1968 (Box 23:459)
      - Shanahan, Michael, undated (Box 23:460)
      - Shea, Joseph, 1966-1968 (Box 23:461-464)
      - Shea, Richard H., 1967 (Box 24)
      - Sherman, G., undated (Box 25:465)
      - Singley, William P, undated (Box 25:466)
      - Slivka, Sigrid, 1968-1971 (Box 25:467)
      - Sossaman, Stephen, undated (Box 25:468)
      - Stein, Jeffrey, undated (Box 25:469)
      - Tharp, Michael Eugene, 1969-1972 (Box 25:470)
      - Trail, Ben D., 1972-1973 (Box 25:471)
      - Tripp, Nathaniel, undated (Box 25:472)
      - Vaughan, Lantry D., undated (Box 25:473)
      - Vinson, Paul A., undated (Box 25:474)
      - Warner, Edward R., 1967 (Box 25:475)
      - Warner, Pate, undated, 1972 (Box 25:476)
      - Watkins, Donald G., undated (Box 25:477)
      - Watts, Carroll, undated (Box 25:478)
      - Weiss, Ritchie, undated (Box 25:479)
      - Weschke, Bernhard P., undated, 1966-1967 (Box 25:480)
      - Whitaker, Tommy J., undated, 1969-1971 (Box 25:481)
      - Whitton, George M., undated (Box 25:482)
      - Willard, Larry, undated, 1972-1973 (Box 25:483)
      - Winslow, John R., Jr., undated, 1969 Dec (Box 25:484)
      - Wolfe, Gerry, 1973 Oct 3 (Box 25:485)
      - Wood, Larry E, undated (Box 25:486)
      - Woods, Richard, undated, 1969 (Box 25:487)
      - Yohn, Tim, undated (Box 25:488)
      - Other Writings, A - G, undated, 1967-1973 (Box 25:489)
      - Other Writings, H - P, undated1965-1973 (Box 25:490)
      - Other Writings, R - Z, undated, 1968-1973 (Box 26:491)
    - First Casualty Press Business
      - Binding and Publishing Information/Notes, undated, 1972 (Box 26:492)
      - Calendar [oversized], 1973 Feb-Jul (Box OS:493)
      - Financial Records and Notes, undated, 1971-1973 (Box 26:494)
      - Medical Aid for Indochina, undated, 1972 (Box 26:495)
      - Peace Group Literature, A - M, undated, 1972-1973 (Box 26:496)
      - Peace Group Literature, N - Z, undated, 1972-1973 (Box 26:497)
      - Poster, Republican National Convention [oversized], 1972 (Box OS:498)
      - Vietnam Veterans Against the War--Connecticut, undated, 1970-1971 (Box 26:499)
      - VVAW/Winter Soldier Organization-- National, undated, 1972-1973 (Box 26:500)
- Series III: Photographs and Drawing, undated
  - Cross, Frank A., Jr., undated
    - Man irrigating field, front view [3.5x5 BW photograph], undated (Box 27:501)
    - Man irrigating field, r. close-up 1 [3.5x5 BW photograph], undated (Box 27:502)
    - Man irrigating field, r. close-up 2 [3.5x5 BW photograph], undated (Box 27:503)
    - Man irrigating field, right view 1 [3.5x5 BW photograph], undated (Box 27:504)
    - Man irrigating field, right view 2 3.5x5 BW photograph], undated (Box 27:505)
    - Man kneeling in field [3.5x5 BW photograph], undated (Box 27:506)
    - Man standing in field w/shovel [3.5x5 BW photograph], undated (Box 27:507)
  - Downey, Mark, undated
    - Man, head & shoulders [8x10 pen & ink drawing, undated (Box 27:508)
  - Ramsdell, Sheldon, undated
    - Larry Rottmann with unidentified man [8x10 BW photograph], undated (Box 27:509)
    - Larry Rottmann with unidentified man, close-up [8x10 BW photograph], undated (Box 27:510)
    - Wayne Karlin at Capitol [5x8 BW photograph], undated (Box 27:511)
  - Shibla, Vernon, undated
    - VVAW medals, Marshall memorial [8x10 BW photograph], undated (Box 27:512)
  - Unidentified, undated
    - Basil Paquet [5x8 BW photograph], undated (Box 27:513)
    - Basil Paquet [5x8 BW photograph], undated (Box 27:514)
    - First Casualty Press sales table [3.5x5 BW photograph], undated (Box 27:515)
    - Man in front of truck [5x8 BW photograph], undated (Box 27:516)
    - Man without legs in wheelchair [8x10 BW photograph], undated (Box 27:517)
    - Man, woman, policewoman [8x10 BW photograph], undated (Box 27:518)
    - Vietnamese man in pile of rocks [8x10 BW photograph], undated (Box 27:519)